[
  {
    "questionNumber": 1,
    "questionText": "The temperature at 12 noon at a certain place was 18° above zero. If it decreases at the rate of 3° per hour at what time it would be 12° below zero?",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 10 am",
      "(b) 12 mid night",
      "(c) 10 pm",
      "(d) 12 noon"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 2,
    "questionText": "Identify the problem with negative numbers as its answer.",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 10+(−4)+8",
      "(b) −4+2+10",
      "(c) −9+(−5)+6",
      "(d) 18+(−12)−6"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 3,
    "questionText": "(-10) + (+7) = ____",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) +3",
      "(b) -3",
      "(c) -17",
      "(d) +17"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 4,
    "questionText": "(-8) + 10 + (-2) = ____",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 2",
      "(b) 8",
      "(c) 0",
      "(d) 20"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 5,
    "questionText": "20 + (-9) + 9 = ____",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 20",
      "(b) 29",
      "(c) 11",
      "(d) 38"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 6,
    "questionText": "(−5)−(−18)= __________",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 13",
      "(b) −13",
      "(c) 23",
      "(d) −23"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 7,
    "questionText": "(−100)−0+100= _________",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 0",
      "(b) 200",
      "(c) 100",
      "(d) −200"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 8,
    "questionText": "Which of the following expressions is equal to −30?",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) (−6)×(+5)",
      "(b) −20−(−5×2)",
      "(c) (6×10)−(6×5)",
      "(d) (2×5)+(4×5)"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 9,
    "questionText": "Which property is illustrated by the equation: (5×2)+(5×5)=5×(2+5)",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) Associative",
      "(b) Distributive",
      "(c) Commutative",
      "(d) Closure"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 10,
    "questionText": "Which of the following does not represent an integer?",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 0÷(−7)",
      "(b) 20÷(−4)",
      "(c) (−9)÷3",
      "(d) (-12)÷5"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 11,
    "questionText": "The set of integers is not closed under",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) Addition",
      "(b) Multiplication",
      "(c) Subtraction",
      "(d) Division"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 12,
    "questionText": "The place value of 3 in 85.073 is ________.",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) Thousandths",
      "(b) Tenths",
      "(c) Hundredths",
      "(d) Thousands"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 13,
    "questionText": "To convert grams into kilograms, we have to divide it by",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 100",
      "(b) 1000",
      "(c) 10",
      "(d) 10000"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 14,
    "questionText": "The decimal representation of 30 kg and 43 g is ______ kg.",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 30.43",
      "(b) 30.043",
      "(c) 30.0043",
      "(d) 30.430"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 15,
    "questionText": "3 / 5 =",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 0.06",
      "(b) 0.006",
      "(c) 0.6",
      "(d) 6"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 16,
    "questionText": "0.009 is equal to",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 0.90",
      "(b) 0.900",
      "(c) 0.090",
      "(d) 0.00900"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 17,
    "questionText": "78.56 _____ 78.57",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) >",
      "(b) <",
      "(c) =",
      "(d) ≠"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 18,
    "questionText": "Between which two whole numbers 1.7 lies?",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 1 and 2",
      "(b) 1 and 7",
      "(c) 2 and 3",
      "(d) 3 and 4"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 19,
    "questionText": "Subtract 1.35 from 3.51",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 8.64",
      "(b) 2.16",
      "(c) 6.21",
      "(d) 4.86"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 20,
    "questionText": "A frog jumps 5.3 cm in one jump. The distance travelled by the frog in 10 jumps is ____________.",
    "question_images": [],
    "option_with_images_": [
      "(a) 53.5 cm",
      "(b) 0.53 cm",
      "(c) 53.0 cm",
      "(d) 530 cm"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "C"
  }
]